popscreen.com 2018-06-29

# PopScreen Privacy Policy

**Your privacy is critically important to us. At PopScreen we have a few fundamental principles:**

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

**Below is our privacy policy, which incorporates these goals:**

PopScreen, Inc. ("PopScreen") may operate several websites that enhance our product offering to you. It is PopScreen's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, PopScreen collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. PopScreen's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how PopScreen's visitors use its website. From time to time, PopScreen may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

PopScreen also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. PopScreen does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to PopScreen's websites choose to interact with PopScreen in ways that require PopScreen to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that PopScreen gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at PopScreen.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, PopScreen collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with PopScreen. PopScreen does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

PopScreen may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, PopScreen may monitor the most popular accounts/users on the PopScreen.com site. PopScreen may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, PopScreen does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

PopScreen discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on PopScreen's behalf or to provide services available at PopScreen's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using PopScreen's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. PopScreen will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, PopScreen discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when PopScreen believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of PopScreen, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a PopScreen website and have supplied your email address, PopScreen may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with PopScreen and our products. We primarily use our various blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. PopScreen takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. PopScreen uses cookies to help PopScreen identify and track visitors, their usage of PopScreen website, and their website access preferences. PopScreen visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Popscreen's websites, with the drawback that certain features of PopScreen's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by PopScreen and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, PopScreen may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in PopScreen's sole discretion. PopScreen encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a popscreen.com account, you should also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Note:** We'd like to thank Automattic for making their Privacy Policy available to us. Here's a link to them [automattic.com](http://www.automattic.com/).
